Let's drill the footwork for the Egyptian walk.
So we're going to start.
I'm going to turn my back towards you.
We're going to start with our weight on the left foot.
We're going to step - keep the arms out away from the body.
Keep the knees bent, belly button pulled in, chest lifted shoulder blades down and back.
Good, we're going to step forward on the right foot and bring the left foot to meet it here.
Step and touch.
Take it back: step, touch.
Step, touch.
Step, together.
Forward.
Keep the knees bent, belly button pulled in.
Step, together.
Good.
Still going forward.
And step, together.
Step, together.
So, try to visualize that you're walking across a pond on lily pads and you don't want to get your feet wet.
So the foot's not out here, the feet are always step, and then together.
Step, together, step, together.
As you step, don't let your ankle fall out.
Keep the weight on that toe, keep that ankle pulled in nice and strong.
Good.
Step, together.
Even if you're taking tiny steps make sure those toes come together.